As the story goes,
the Li family has lost three wives in succession.
They appear as soon as night falls.
And not long ago,
Li's daughter, Mengzhu, also died.
They say only a ghost marriage
can appease the dead's resentment.
The Classic of Lu Ban states,
"A door taller than the hall
means the family line will fall."
The architectural layout of the Li mansion
is actually designed to end their bloodline.
The layout of the front hall is odd too.
The front road forms the 'fire' character.
When the yearly curse strikes,
disaster follows.
When building a house,
why curse the people living in it
with such endless misfortune?
Kneel!
Heaven and Earth as witness,
let the souls return.
Yin and Yang in harmony,
bringing eternal peace.
A ghost marriage sealed with wine,
their destinies bound.
Li Mengzhu and Jiang Huai are now husband and wife.
Escort them to the mourning hall!
A ghost!
The madam's ghost has returned!
I'm just a storyteller.
How did I end up like this?
It all started three days ago.
Such a beautiful bride.
Will you return to the Palace of the
King of Hell
and be a ghost couple for eternity?
Master.
We're still five li away from Lijia Town.
It's getting pretty late.
Let's just make do and spend the night here.
It seems...
...we have no other choice.
We'll spend the night here.
There's a ghost, Master!
It's all your fault!
I went through so much trouble to set that trap,
and you just had to ruin it!
Once I catch the killer behind
the King of Hell's wedding, you'll pay!
The King of Hell's wedding...
The corpse exhibits adipocere.
The lividity is dark brown.
You were poisoned.
Clothes scented with twelve spices.
Very refined.
Your family runs a spice shop.
The King of Hell got away.
It's all your fault.
Be quiet.
What's he doing?
This is my master's ultimate technique.
Five-Sense Deduction.
My master uses sight,
hearing,
smell,
taste,
and touch.
Combining these five senses,
and through meditation,
he can discover overlooked clues.
Just wait and see.
You're the young lady of the spice shop.
After being poisoned,
you were forced to marry the King of Hell.
You never agreed to marry him.
Then who was that just now?
I get it now.
He's awake.
Spouting mumbo jumbo.
I think you're in cahoots with the King of Hell.
Ow, ow, ow!
Let's talk this out.
Could you let go first?
Spill it!
How about I help you solve the case?
Master, help!
Let go, let go, let go!
Let me see.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
As long as you're okay.
How will you solve the case?
This female corpse...
...you placed it here on purpose...
...to lure out that King of Hell, right?
Yes.
For over a month now,
newlywed brides in Lijia Town
have been dropping dead.
And while waiting to be buried,
their bodies mysteriously vanished.
The villagers all say
if a bride catches the King of Hell's eye,
her body will be taken by him.
I don't buy it at all.
This King of Hell taking a bride is pure nonsense.
If you ask me,
it's just murder for money.
I was going to catch him red-handed today.
It's all your fault
for ruining my plan.
Who?
Who's there?
You are...
Inspector Mu!
Old newsman!
Why is it you again?
How many times do I have to say it?
While the police are investigating,
you must not spread false information!
Stop making things up in your tabloid.
I didn't! This is...
Just go, go, go.
Don't interfere with my case.
No, but you...
- Give me back my pen! - I don't have it!
Go away!
My family heirloom pen! I...
Um,
Lady Inspector,
are you looking for that King of Hell?
I know where he is.
Just making things up as you go?
The King of Hell...
...is eight chi tall,
wearing white-edged cloth shoes.
On his hands,
is adipocere from the corpse's face.
If you chase him west for five li,
the first person you meet
will be the King of Hell.
How do you know that?
Master...
Not only do I know where he is,
I also know his motive for impersonating
the King of Hell to kill brides.
What is it?
Tell me! Don't keep me in suspense!
Once you catch him yourself,
check his pockets,
and you'll have the answer.
Also,
if you don't go after him now,
it'll be too late.
You should've said so!
Master,
do you really know the King of Hell?
Then who is he?
Of course I don't know him!
Stop imagining things!
Dry weather,
beware of fire!
Run five li west.
The first you meet is the King of Hell.
Eight chi tall,
white-edged cloth shoes.
He has adipocere on his hands.
That's him.
Dry weath-
Don't move!
You're the King of Hell's wedding killer!
I'm innocent! I'm innocent!
I'm just a night watchman!
I'm no King of Hell!
Master.
Are you sure about this?
How can a watchman be the King of Hell?
He was caught stealing corpses
as the King of Hell. Get up!
The ruined temple is in the wilderness
with nowhere to hide.
His safest bet
was to flee to Lijia Town
and become himself again.
Still denying it?
You specifically targeted the wives
of wealthy families
just for this gold jewelry.
It was our boss.
He set his sights on the gold
in the Li family's shop.
He told me to...
Who's there?
Now the fake King of Hell will meet
the real King of Hell.
Posing as the King of Hell to steal gold
was just their diversion.
Actually, their real target
is the Li family's gold shop.
Life for life, gold breeds gold